export const data = [
    {
        language:"English",
        button:"Test you English level!!"
    },
    {
        language:"HIndi",
        button:"Test you Hindi level!!"
    },
    {
        language:"Punjabi",
        button:"Test you Punjabi level!!"
    },
];

export const testDataEnglish=[
{
    id:"1",
    question:"Fate smiles ...... those who untiringly grapple with stark realities of life.",
    options:[
    "with",
    "over",
    "on",
    "round"
    ],
    answer:3
},
{
    id:"2",
    question:"The miser gazed ...... at the pile of gold coins in front of him.",
    options:[
        "avidly",
        "admiringly",
        "thoughtfully",
        "earnestly"
    ],
    answer:1
},
{
    id:"3",
    question:"Catching the earlier train will give us the ...... to do some shopping.",
    options:[
        "chance",
        "luck",
        "possibility",
        "occasion"],
        answer:1
    
},
{
    id:"4",
    question:"I saw a ...... of cows in the field.",
options:[
        "group",
        "herd",
        "swarm",
        "flock"
],
answer:2
},
{
    id:"5",
    question:"The grapes are now ...... enough to be picked.",
    options:[
        "ready",
        "mature",
        "ripe",
        "advanced"
    ],
    answer:3
},
{
    id:"6",
    question:"Success in this examination depends ...... hard work alone.",
    options:[
        "at",
        "over",
        "for",
        "on"
    ],
    answer:4
},
{
    id:"7",
    question:"My uncle decided to take ...... and my sister to the market.",
    options:[
        "I",
        "mine",
        "me",
        "myself"
    ],
    answer:3
},
{
    id:"8",
    question:"If you smuggle goods into the country, they may be ...... by the customs authority.",
    options:[
        "possessed",
        "punished",
        "confiscated",
        "fined"
    ],
    answer:3
},
{
    id:"9",
    question:"Man does not live by ...... alone.",
    options:[
        "food",
        "bread",
        "meals",
        "diet"
    ],
    answer:2
},
{
    id:"10",
    question:"Piyush behaves strangely at times and, therefore, nobody gets ...... with him.",
    options:[
        "about",
        "through",
        "along",
        "up"
    ],
    answer:3
},

];